Rizky lan Indiarto

Malang, Indonesia, 65144 | +62-851-569-379-59 | rizkyian78@gmail.com | Indonesian,

About Me

I am a Software Engineer, and Digital Nomad who has freelanced and worked full-time at startups to grow their platform businesses.

As a Software ,I am working on several project, for instance Pertamina Direct Buying, Pertamina VMI, System Management Hotel, and lastly working on Payment Gateway. aside working on project i have mentoring student from vocational highschool in indonesia related programming specifically using javascript, golang, python, Kotlin currently interested in web3.

Lastly, I am multilingual (English, Japanese, Indonesian, French) and able to collaborate with diverse teams to create global products.

Work Experience

Software Engineer (Internet Payment Gateway)

Sep 2021 - Present

Brankas Pte Ltd

Remote, Malang

- Integrating Payment gateway with many payment method, for instance LinkAja, OVO, allopay, Visa, Master Card, and etc
- Planned development with team how to integrate payment and implement new feature of Brankas PG
- Troubleshooting error and bug when happened in production environment after release
- Implemented SNAP (Indonesian Open API Payment Standard)
- Implemented FDS (Fraud Detection System)
- Create Settlement report
- Create validation card payment with 2C2P
- Implemented Tokenization for card payment
- Implemented Oauth service for authorization
- Become Speaker in GoJakarta (GRPC VS RESTful API)
- Tools: Kubernetes, Docker, Typescript, GO, React, Material UI, Drone CI

Achievement

- Successfully handled humongous transaction when "Allobank Festival" conducted by Bank Megas. The
 festival invited 2 distinguished Korean group band RED VELVET, and NCT Dream as in Indonesian fans
 is huge. We able to complete it flawlessly with processed > 800 million IDR (\$53404) in single day
- Successfully handled humongous transaction when "CXO Media Live On Stage!" conducted by Bank Megas. The festival invited 2 distinguished Korean group band Taeyong, and Epik High as in Indonesian fans is huge. We able to complete it flawlessly with processed > 2.5 Billion IDR (\$1700000) in single day
- Able to Handle with Yokke Payment Gateway with minimum transaction of 800 million IDR (\$53404) / month
- Our Payment Gateway Currently being used with more 50 merchant for instance, Bukalapak, Livin Mandiri. etc

Freelance Software Engineer

PT. Nusantara Teknologi.

Sep 2021 - Nov 2022 Remote, Indonesia

- Act as Freelance Software Engineer. Project that i handled :
 - TokoTalk LMS (Library Management System)
 - Curriculum Lead as well mentor in Nusa Development Program

Achievement

Make Front End and Backend Curriculum and still being used until now

Software Engineer

Jul 2020 - September 2021

PT. Nusantara Teknologi.

Jakarta, Indonesia

- Collaborated in application development by utilizing Typescript, NodeJS and Express as a backend framework, AWS as a cloud service provider, and MySQL
- Act as Full Stack Engineer. engineering level for sustainable IT solution company with various achievement in forms of projects and products. Project that i handled:
 - Siprus (Gov-owned Real Estate)
 - Pertamina VMI (Gov-owned Oil and Gas Company)
 - System Management Hotel
 - Telkom Neucentrix (Gov-owned telecommunication company)
 - LDX (Japanese Garment Company)

Achievement

System Management Hotel currently being used within Nusantech Group in all over Java Island

Industrial Engineer

Jan 2021 - Jul 2022

GLINTS Remote

- Mock Technical Interveiw: Conduct a Basic Javascript assessment for Final Period Glints Academy Student and giving them some advice.
- Participating in Hackathon conducted by GLINTS

Education

Binar Academy Bootcamp

Feb 2020 - May 2020

Backend Engineering

Remote

Brawijaya University
Bachelor Degree - Political Science

Sep 2013 - Dec 2018 Malang, Indonesia **Programming:** Python, JavaScript, Kotlin, No-SQL, SQL, Swift, Node.js, Go, TypeScript, Kubernetes, Microservices, RabbitMQ, gRPC, GraphQL, Automation, SDLC, Docker, React, Flutter, Jenkins, CI/CD, Spring boot (Kotlin), Drone CI, GitHub, Jenkins, Firebase, Vercel

Platforms: Linux (Ubuntu), Mac OS, Windows

Software: X Code, Docker GUI, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ

Professional Organizations: Dev-C Malang, GoJakarta (Golang), Leo Club Malang (Charity Organization)

Communication: Public Speaking, Negotiation, Presentations (large and small audiences) **Languages:** Bahasa (Native), English (Professional), Japanese (beginner), French (beginner)

Relevant Course

• SwiftUI & IOS Engineer: The Complete App Development Bootcamp

- Automating Infrastructure on Google Cloud with Terraform
- Integrate with Machine Learning APIs
- Serverless Firebase Development
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass
- React JavaScript
- React Native: Advanced Concepts
- Golang Fundamentals